Guide to the Arthur E. Scott photograph collection, 1910-1976
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 5: Scrapbooks, 1918-1946; (27 volumes)
  - The Patent Office series, March 3, 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - Navy's Deep Water Sea Diving School, Navy Yard, Washington, D.C., March 8, 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - Air Hostess Training School, March 22, 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - "Secret Crop Report", United States Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Agricultural Economics, March 20, 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - U.S. postage stamp production series, April 25, 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - U.S. postage stamp production series (continued), April 25, 1944 (Volume 8B)
  - Making prosthetics, May 10, 1944 (Volume 8B)
  - National Archives series, January 6, 1946 (Volume 8B)
  - Navy Special Devices Division, May 19, 1944 (Volume 8B)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt photo for Sunday Star, January 21, 1945 (Volume 8B)
  - War Department posters, June 12, 1944 (Volume 8B)
  - Women's Land Army picking fruit, September 7, 1944 (Volume 8B)
  - Painting the U.S. Capitol building, November 3, 1944 (Volume 8B)
  - Doolittle Raiders return home, September 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Jonathan M. Wainwright returns home, September 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Jonathan M. Wainwright and George C. Marshall in Wainwright's parade, September 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Admiral John S. McCain's body is returned for burial in Arlington National Cemetery, September 9, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Harold H. Burton appointed by Harry S. Truman to U.S. Supreme Court, October 1, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Chester W. Nimitz arrives in Washington, D.C. for a celebration in his honor, October 5, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Harry S. Truman leaves for a tour of six states, October 6, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Harry S. Truman plays photographer, with Arthur E. Scott, October 12, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - George C. Marshall testifies before Congress, October 12, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt presented with a portrait of the late Franklin D. Roosevelt, artist C. C. Beall, October 24, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Albert B. "Happy" Chandler resigns to become baseball high commissioner, October 29, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Miss America, Bess Myers, crowns U.N. Victory Bond Queen, Annie Lou Brock, November 4, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Labor and Management Conference, Washington, D.C., November 5-6, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Poet Ezra Pound faces charges of treason, November 18, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Pearl Harbor hearings, November 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Washington Redskins victory over Pittsburgh Steelers, Sammy Baugh throws a touchdown, December 2, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower with Arthur E. Scott and Oliver Atkins, December 7, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower at Griffith Stadium for Washington Redskins vs. New York Giants football game, December 9, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - George C. Marshall walks through a snow storm to Pearl Harbor Investigation Committee, December 10, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Pearl Harbor hearings, December 12, 1945 (Volume 9)
  - Palestine Inquiry Committee, January 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - "Mile-o'-Dimes" campaign against infantile paralysis opened by Bess Truman, January 14, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Demobilization plans explained before Congress, with Dwight D. Eisenhower and Chester W. Nimitz, January 15, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Harry S. Truman honors George C. Marshall at a testimonial dinner, January 16, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Memorial service for George S. Patton, Jr., Washington National Cathedral, with Dwight D. Eisenhower and Chester W. Nimitz, undated (Volume 10A)
  - Pearl Harbor hearings, January 22, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Celebrities: Caesar Romero, William Bendix, Van Johnson, Angela Landsbury, Van Johnson, at 12th Annual Observance of the Birthday of Franklin D. Roosevelt, with Harry S. Truman and Bess Truman, January 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Women's National Press Club awards for women leaders, including Georgia O'Keefe, February 9, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Disabled American Veterans graduation exercise, American University, Washington D.C., with Dwight D. Eisenhower and Omar N. Bradley, February 10, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower lays a wreath at the Lincoln Memorial, February 12, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Jacob S. Coxey, age 92, of "Coxey's Army" in 1894, testifies against loan to Britain, March 5, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - John L. Lewis and United Mine Workers battle for improved wages and working conditions, March 13, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Gabriela Mistral, 1945 Nobel Poetry Prize winner meets Harry S. Truman, March 16, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Francis Cardinal Spellman, Archbishop of New York, receives honorary Doctor of Laws degree from Georgetown University, March 17, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Harry S. Truman throws out the first pitch of the 1946 baseball season, Griffith Stadium, Washington, D.C., April 16, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Charles Evans Hughes attends funeral services of late Harlan Fisk Stone, Washington National Cathedral, April 25, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower talks with reporters on board "Mayflower", April 26, 1946 (Volume 10A)
  - John L. Lewis, head of United Mine Workers, March, May 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Harry S. Truman meeting with Herbert C. Hoover on world food shortage, March 15, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Navy Proving Ground, May 22, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Harry S. Truman appeals to rail workers to end strike, May 24, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Soft Coal Strike ends, John L. Lewis and Harry S. Truman shake hands, May 29, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Harry S. Truman congratulates Medal of Honor winners, June 14, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Francis Cardinal Spellman address graduating class of the FBI National Academy, with J. Edgar Hoover, June 28, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Memorial Services in honor of Franklin D. Roosevelt, July 1, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Aircraft carrier "Franklin D. Roosevelt", with Arthur E. Scott, July 21, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Mead Committee Hearings, with Arthur E. Scott, July 31, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - Anti-lynching law marches, August 5, 1946 (Volume 10B)
  - House Merchant Marine Committee investigates wartime profits of shipping companies, September 23, 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - Washington, D.C. hotel workers strike, October 11, 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - The "Mayflower", Presidential yacht, offered for sale, October 12, 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - Harry S. Truman lays a wreath at the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, Arlington National Cemetery, November 11, 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - White House News Photographers Association, Fourth Annual Photo Exhibit with Arthur E. Scott, December 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - Harry S. Truman vacation to Florida, with Arthur E. Scott at Fort Jefferson, November 17-23, 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - John L. Lewis, head of United Mine Workers, November 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - Arthur E. Scott photographing John L. Lewis, November 27, 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower for President buttons, "Draft Ike 1948", December 30, 1946 (Volume 11A)
  - Republican Senators hold first pre-session caucus, with Joseph McCarthy and Robert A. Taft, December 30, 1946 (Volume 11B)
  - First Republican-led Congress in 18 years convenes, January 3, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - World War II veterans of the Senate, includes Joseph McCarthy and Henry Cabot Lodge, January 13, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - Eddie Rickenbacker receive a medal, January 23,1947 (Volume 11B)
  - George C. Marshall greats Canada's Governor-General Viscount Alexander and Lady Alexander, February 4, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - Robert A. Taft speaking about budget cut proposal, February 17, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - House members join a drive to appeal legal distinction between men and women, February 17, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - George C. Marshall with Crown Prince Amir Saud of Saudi Arabia, February 18, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - Destroying damaged paper money at the Bureau of Engraving and Printing, Washington, D.C., June 2, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - Unveiling of a statue of George Washington at Washington National Cathedral, February 23, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - George C. Marshall greets India's first ambassador to the United States, Asof Ali, February 26, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - Trygve Lie visits George C. Marshall, February 27, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - White House Correspondents' Association annual dinner, March 4, 1947 (Volume 11B)
  - Navy Deep Sea Diving School, March 13, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Foreign Service Institute, March 23, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Un-American Activities Committee, March 26-27, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Albert Gore argues against tax cuts, March 27, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Arthur E. Scott at a podium, April 5, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Harry S. Truman with Washington Senator's baseball team owner, Clark C. Griffith, April 9, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Harry S. Truman greets George C. Marshall on Marshall's return from Moscow Meeting of the Big Four Foreign Ministers, April 26, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Meeting of ten top leaders of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, May 1, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Arthur E. Scott injury report, left ankle injured while on assignment, May 12, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Arthur E. Scott with Jack Dempsey and Gene Tunney at Colombian Country Club golf match, May 17, 1947 (Volume 11C)
  - Remembrance of the Colombian Exhibition in Chicago 1893, May 25,1933 (Volume 12)
  - Training at Camp Meade, April 1918 (Volume 12)
  - Photographs of everyday life in Soviet Russia, famine, October 1921 (Volume 12)
  - Warren G. Harding and Mrs. Harding go to church, February 13, 1921 (Volume 12)
  - Warren G. Harding inauguration, March 5, 1921 (Volume 12)
  - Georges Clemenceau visits Mount Vernon, Virginia, the U.S. Capitol building, Arlington National Cemetery, December 4-7, 1922 (Volume 12)
  - Serbian Royal Wedding of Princess Marie of Roumania and King Alexander of Yugo-Slavia, June 17, 1922 (Volume 12)
  - Mrs. W. H. Felton [Rebecca Latimer Felton] first woman to occupy a seat in the U.S. Senate, November 18, 1922 (Volume 12)
  - Army tests helicopter, January 16, 1923 (Volume 12)
  - U.S.S. Cruiser Trenton is launched, April 17, 1923 (Volume 12)
  - Pancho Villa murder, July 26, 1923 (Volume 12)
  - European royal families, 1923 (Volume 12)
  - Turkey scenes, January-March 1923 (Volume 12)
  - William T. Cosgrave of the Irish Free State in New York City, February 2, 1928 (Volume 13)
  - European royal families, 1928 (Volume 13)
  - William Howard Taft's body lies in state in U.S. Capitol building rotunda, March 11, 1930 (Volume 13)
  - Nazi party in Germany, October 4, 1934 (Volume 13)
  - Albert Einstein, pacifist movement, arriving in Chicago, March 1931 (Volume 13)
  - Death of John Philip Sousa, March 6, 1932 (Volume 13)
  - Dresses of First Ladies exhibit at Smithsonian Institution, February 18, 1933 (Volume 13)
  - King Albert of Belgium dies, February 1934 (Volume 13)
  - Emperor Kang Teh of Manchutikuo, coronation, March 11, 1934 (Volume 13)
  - Mount Rushmore partially complete, head of Washington completed, March 15, 1934 (Volume 13)
  - Boulder Dam completed, September 12, 1936 (Volume 13)
  - Proposal for a Washington National Airport at Gravelly Point, November 19, 1938 (Volume 13)
  - Political cartoons, Joseph Stalin, Adolph Hitler, January 1, 1940 (Volume 14)
  - John N. Garner and Senators pass through Statuary Hall in the U.S. Capitol building to hear Franklin D. Roosevelt address a joint session of Congress, January 3, 1940 (Volume 14)
  - Charles L. McNary nominated for Republican Presidential ticket with Wendell Willkie, June 28, 1940 (Volume 14)
  - Democratic National Convention, Chicago Stadium, July 19, 1940 (Volume 14)
  - Anti-conscription protests, Youth Committee Against War, August 1, 1940 (Volume 14)
  - Conscription bill and draft registration, September-October 1940 (Volume 14)
  - Political cartoons, Adolph Hitler, July 1940 (Volume 14)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt and Winston Churchill meet aboard the H.M.S. Prince of Wales/U.S.S. Augusta, August 14-15, 1941 (Volume 14)
  - Passage of the Neutrality Act, November 13, 1941 (Volume 14)
  - Troops guarding the War Department after news of Pearl Harbor bombing, December 7, 1941 (Volume 14)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt declares war against Japan, December 8, 1941 (Volume 14)
  - United States troops in Iceland, February 13, 1942 (Volume 14)
  - Soldiers on a ship of convoy somewhere in the Pacific, January 3, 1942 (Volume 14)
  - Defense preparations in Hawaii, January 10, 1942 (Volume 14)
  - First meeting of the National War Labor Board, January 16, 1942 (Volume 14)
  - Bombardier Training Air Corps Advance Flying School, Albuquerque, New Mexico, February 4, 1942 (Volume 14)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt first President to fly in a plane while in office, visits to North Africa, meeting with Winston Churchill, January 27, 1943 (Volume not numbered)
  - Celebrities at Franklin D. Roosevelt 's Birthday Ball, Edgar Bergen and Charley McCarthy, Roy Rogers, Loretta Young, January 30, 1943 (Volume not numbered)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, Eleanor Roosevelt lay a wreath at the Lincoln Memorial, February 12, 1943 (Volume not numbered)
  - U.S. Coast Guard cutter "Campbell" damaged in battle with U-boat, undated (Volume not numbered)
  - Douglas MacArthur at Tadji, New Guinea, April 26, 1944 (Volume not numbered)
  - Nazi prisoner with resemblance to Adolph Hitler, Italy, May 19, 1944 (Volume not numbered)
  - Hundreds of Nazi prisoners march to an internment camp in England, June 9, 1944 (Volume not numbered)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt letter accepting nomination for a fourth term in office, July 11, 1944 (Volume not numbered)
  - King George VI knights F. W. de Guingand, October 19, 1944 (Volume not numbered)
  - Joseph Stalin and Winston Churchill at "Big Three" conference, Crimea, Russia [Yalta Conference], February 12, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt addresses a joint session of Congress about his visit to Yalta Conference, March 1, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Swearing in of Harry S. Truman as President, April 12, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Benito Mussolini hanging after his execution, May 1, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Winston Churchill, President Harry S. Truman, Generalissimo Joseph Stalin outside of Churchill's residence before dinner party (Volume not numbered)
  - Japanese documents of surrender, September 2, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Chester W. Nimitz welcome parade and medal, October 5, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Harry S. Truman presents fourteen Medals of Honor, October 5, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Japanese war crimes in the Philippines, October 8, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Japanese war criminals numbered in order of importance, October 12, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - Anton Dostler executed by firing squad in Italy, December 13, 1945 (Volume not numbered)
  - New housing project in rubble of Hiroshima, Japan, February 11, 1946 (Volume not numbered)
- Series 6: Realia, 1950s-1960s; (Box 28)
  This series contains realia.
  - Realia, 1950s-1960s (Box 28)
    Contains photographic supplies, including labeled film canisters.